#### Contact

Clermont/Mount Dora Central Florida stacypjcsn@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/stacy-lynn-branton-coco-b7784921 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Acute Care Hospitals

# Stacy Lynn Branton-Coco

Travel Nurse at NuWest Group Holdings, LLC. Jacobi Bronx NY travel RN FRONTLINE

Orlando, Florida Area

## Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a dmonstrated history in working in healthcare industry and hospital. Also as a travel RN .Cardiac icc icu pcu RN with16 years experience. Charge RN for 10 years .Travel RN for 5 years. Computer trained preceptor and float team. Clinical Education and Nursing Management. Patient , Family and Nurse advocacy. Just completed a very fufilling job in Hospice. RN Case Manager for Hospice. Multiple skills in nursing. Being travel nurse float to all units, presently Rehab /PCU stepdown.. night shift supervisor

### Experience

NuWest Group Holdings, LLC Travel Nurse April 2020 - Present (3 months) New York, New York, United States

Gulf Coast Health Care, LLC RN December 2018 - Present (1 year 7 months) Pensacola, Florida Area

Cornerstone Hospice & Palliative Care, Inc. RN Case Manager December 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 3 months) Florida

Shared with CMRN weekdays. I was CMRN On Friday -Sunday. I was with home based hospice patients and families. Assessment talk with the patient and family to keep updated. Ordered medicatios and supplies. Discussed with Dr on call any changes or concerns. Charted.

just left cornerstone hospice RN Hospice Case Manager

December 2016 - February 2018 (1 year 3 months)

Nightingale Nurses

Travel RN

October 2014 - July 2016 (1 year 10 months)

Louisiana

Cardiac RN .charge nurse....preceptor...

Louisiana heart hospital

Rn

May 2014 - October 2014 (6 months)

Lacombe, Louisiana

Tele step down icu pcu

### East Jefferson General Hospital

Rn

March 2014 - May 2014 (3 months)

Telemetry step down unit ICU Pcu ... great place to work. The whole experience has been incredible. Best team work ive seen in a long time.

#### TRAVEL RN

ICU/ CARDIAC CARE/ Acute Care RN Travel

March 2013 - March 2014 (1 year 1 month)

USA

new companies new experiences.. about time to leave FL... see new places with my honeys...

### PRO-MED STAFFING COMPANY

PRN RN

May 2012 - January 2013 (9 months)

for Citrus Hospital and Citrus Hospice.. Med Surg Floor at Hospital and In Hospital Hospice patients. Continuation of Hospice Care for patients in home settings..End of life care.

travel rn nite nite RN travel 2002 - 2013 (11 years)

cardiac stepdown, pcu, med sx tele RN charge RN

Northside Hospital RN CDU/PCU/MED SX February 2012 - June 2012 (5 months)

#### ..CDU/TELE/PCU/ ALL MED SURG

Complete patient care from admission to discharge. Followed all MD orders. Explained/Teaching of any medications, procedures to patient and family. Developed Care Plan for each patient. Assessments, EKG's, pre and post op procedures/surgeries.

#### **HHC Homebound**

RN

February 2011 - November 2011 (10 months)

In patient HHC ..total patient care including medications, all ADL's. Teaching patient and family members how to continue care with or with out HHC.. Palliative Care for end of life patients. Assisting patient , family, and other members of family or friends grief process and how to assist in the care of their loved one.

### Select Specialty Hospital

Registered Nurse

March 2010 - December 2010 (10 months)

Managed care for post-operative patients through their discharge. Developed patient care plans, including assessments, evaluations, and nursing diagnoses. Responsible for primary care, case management, and medication management. Ordered and read lab tests, x-rays, MRIs, ultrasounds, and EKGs. Supported patients with customized teaching tools. Assessed patients and documented patient histories. Assisted patients with daily functions, bathing, dressing, hygiene, and grooming. Assisted doctors with surgeries, non-invasive procedures, examinations, and treatment. Assisted and performed wound care.

### Baptist Hospital

Registered Nurse Charge II

June 2002 - March 2010 (7 years 10 months)

Responsible for primary care, case management, and medication management for 5-6 patients on night shift. Managed patients on Telemetry and most were on some form of IV therapy for specific treatments. Assessed patients and documented patient histories. Evaluated patient care needs, prioritized treatment, and maintained patient flow. Evaluated health education needs and provided necessary training and instruction. Coordinated with doctors and other staff to develop care plans for patients. As charge RN on night shift, I was responsible for making schedule, arranging meeting with

management, orienting new employees, and precepting student nurses. In charge of the entire 30 bed unit with staff of RNs to students. Performed monthly inventory and maintain office and medical supply counts. Multi-tasked general office duties.

Skills

Solid understanding of methods and procedures for treatment

Intravenous therapy

Patient evaluation and intervention

Advanced problem solving skills

Great bedside manner

Patient and family advocacy

Obtaining and charting vital signs

Pre/post-surgical care

Wound cleaning and care

NG tube insertion and removal

Proficient in flow sheet charting

Acute and rehabilitative care

Tracheotomy care

Colostomy care

Foley catheter insertion and removal

Minor surgery assistance

### Education

Pensacola Junior College

2002 Associate, Nursing; RN studies · (1998 - 2002)

Southeastern Louisiana University

nursing prerequisites, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse (1987 - 1988)